





Ranjith AR Ranjith AR @ Featured Technical Writer seeking roles in Technical Writing, Technical Documentation, Technical Editing, Copy Editing, Content Editing, Adobe FrameMaker, Arbortext Epic Editor, Adobe RoboHelp, Snagit, Photoshop, MS Paint, Jira, Sharepoint, DITA, HTML, XML, MSTP, ASD-STE Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 7 Month(s) Current Designation: Technical Writer Current Company: Sonovision-Aetos Notice Period: 15 Days or less Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Aerospace] Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming Maintenance Role: Technical Writer Industry: IT-Software/Software Services Marital Status: Married Key Skills: Technical Writer, Technical Writing, Technical Documentation, Technical Editing, Copy Editing, Content Editing, Adobe FrameMaker, Arbortext Epic Editor, Adobe RoboHelp, Snagit, Photoshop, MS Paint, Jira, Sharepoint, DITA, HTML, XML, MSTP, ASD-STE

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Verified : Number | Email - id

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills

Summary

Result-oriented Professional with 3.6 years of experience in Technical Writing, Technical Documentation, Technical Editing, Copy Editing, Content Editing, Adobe Frame Maker, Arbortext Epic Editor, Adobe Robo Help, Snagit, Photoshop, MS Paint, Jira, Sharepoint, DITA, HTML, XML, MSTP, ASD-STE.

Work Experience

Sonovision-Aetos as Technical Writer

Nov 2018 to Till Date

Result-oriented Professional with 3.6 years of experience in Technical Writing, Technical Documentation, Technical Editing, Copy Editing, Content Editing, Adobe Frame Maker, Arbortext Epic Editor, Adobe Robo Help, Snagit, Photoshop, MS Paint, Jira, Sharepoint, DITA, HTML, XML, MSTP, ASD-STE.

Sonovision Aetos Pvt Ltd as Technical Writer -IT

Nov 2018 to Jul 2020

Creation and revision of installation guides, user manuals, help files and release notes.

Analysis of the requirements of the customer.

Analysis of the audience

Analysis of the product using various resources.

Interviewing the SMEs on various aspects to be known.

Designing or structuring the template following style guides, ASD-STE and MSTP

Creation of the content and integration of the graphics following S1000D and DITA specifications.

Information mapping the content.

Reviewing the document by various experts.

Sonovision-Aetos as Technical Writer

Nov 2018 to Jul 2020

Alten India Pvt Ltd as Technical Author

Nov 2016 to Sep 2018

Creation, revision and modification of IPC documents using S1000D specifications.

Analyzing the modifications and applying it on the product.

Creation of various documents, COC, LMP, MPM, RFI/R, and SB following ATA 100 and ASD-STE 100 specifications.

Integration of illustration as per the modifications

Training the beginners on the workflow, analytical skills and documentation procedure.

Reviewing the peer work

Important

· Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E (Aerospace) from NOORUL ISLAM UNIVERSITY, Kanyakumari in 2015

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
ADOBE FRAMEMAKER	
Arbortext Epic Editor	
MS WORD	
ADOBE ROBOHELP	
MS Visio	
SnagIT, Photoshop	
MS PAINT	
MS POWERPOINT	
JIRA, Sharepoint	
SVN version control	
DITA, HTML, XML	
MSTP, ASD-STE	

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Kannada				
Tamil				
Malayalam				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.